it's actually estimated that 90 of
americans don't eat enough fruits and
veggies which of course are abundant in
vitamins and minerals and as a result
about one-third of the u.s population is
at risk of being deficient in at least
one micronutrient so to land on the best
multivitamins for women we've been
looking at a ton of brands like dozens
and dozens of them from the best known
to the newest up-and-comers to see what
is the best multivitamin for women
overall but in addition several other
categories like female athletes women
over 50 and more if you want to see the
full written version of this article so
you can go through it at your own pace
or if you want to check out some of the
studies that we're going to be talking
about in this video make sure to google
the full written version of this video
with barbin plus best women's
multivitamins and if you decide you want
to purchase any of these products you
can just click on the links to the
products in the description below
they're right here on youtube one more
thing before we get into it i just want
to make it clear this is not medical
advice make sure you speak to your
doctor or at least nutritionist or a
dietitian before making any changes to
your weight loss or nutrition or
supplement regimen so what's the best
overall well sometimes less is more
especially when it comes down to what
you put in your body a good multivitamin
gives you what you need without giving
you a lot of stuff that you don't which
is why we landed on rituals essential
for women rituals simplified its formula
to include what they use it to be just
the essentials one of the multis
contains just nine ingredients but they
work in harmony to help keep your body
running optimally the list of nutrients
includes stuff like vitamin d omega-3
magnesium iron and a lot more a lot of
interesting greens for bone health like
vitamin k2 that said it's possible given
this is a relatively short ingredients
list that if there's something in
particular you want to supplement with
it may not be on here so just make sure
you take a close look at the label
before you click purchase next up is the
best multivitamin for women over 50 who
may want to look for a multivitamin that
has links to healthy energy levels
supporting bone health promotes immune
function this is what rituals
multivitamin for women over 50 has done
it's formulated to provide eight
ingredients that include vitamin d k2 e
b12 omega-3 born magnesium virtual packs
of formulas with a lot of vitamins and
minerals in good doses as well and they
purposely leave out some ingredients
like vitamin c and calcium in this case
since people are unlikely to not be
getting enough of those two ingredients
if they're consuming a healthy diet this
is more about giving you vitamins and
minerals that women over 50 tend to fall
short in so it's a really nice
interesting minimalist approach to
nutrition make sure you take a close
look at the ingredients list and make
sure it's got everything you need as
directed by your doctor but overall we
found that across the market this is the
best multivitamin format over 50. next
up is the best women's multivitamin
gummy if you're looking to add a little
flavor to your daily multivitamin a
gummy supplement can be a great way to
go and this going multi is the best that
we tried out smartypants daily organic
gummy this product packs 15 essential
nutrients including omega-3s vitamin d3
vitamin c b12
in one for gummy serving in addition it
contains biotin which may help with hair
skin and male health benefit many women
take separate supplements for already
spider plants also include zinc which
can help with immune support plus a ton
of the ingredients are organic there's a
wide variety of flavors you can choose
from and you can get them in a nice
hefty 120 pill bottle so you just need
one for the rest of the month as the
best women's multivitamin with iron iron
deficiency does affect more women than
men so it's not uncommon for women's
multivitamin supplements to emphasize
iron our favorite is legion's triumph
iron deficiency can affect women during
their period and during pregnancy and
some may find it important to have a
supplement that includes iron so they
don't have to take a separate iron
supplement altogether legion triumph
includes 10 milligrams of iron per
serving which is 60 of your recommended
daily intake and on top of that you'll
find 22 key vitamins and minerals like
vitamins a c d and e k 1 k 2 b vitamins
plus calcium magnesium biotin zinc and
iron this list of micronutrients is one
of the most comprehensive we've seen
although it is worth noting that it's a
bit more expensive than a lot of other
multivitamins on the market next up the
best women's daily multi is easy on the
stomach has all the essential nutrients
for women and requires just two capsules
per day it's vegetables essential it's
got plenty of nice traceable ingredients
like folate omega-3s vitamin d vitamin
k2 all of these are selected because
they're considered the foundation for
better health for women targeting brain
health bone health red blood cell
formulation and antioxidant support plus
ritual has an interesting delayed
release formula that makes sure the
ingredients largely get released in the
intestine as opposed to the stomach as
the intestine may be a better place for
you to be absorbing these particular
nutrients and lastly they're this nice
minty capsule in here that keeps the
flavor pretty pleasant for something
that contains omega-3s from algae so how
about the best women's multivitamin for
energy whether you're working through a
tough training schedule or just seems to
be hitting a lull in the afternoon a
multivitamin with a lot of ingredients
like coq10 and b vitamins could help to
maintain healthy energy levels legions
is our favorite for this legion contains
a pretty comprehensive list of vitamins
and minerals 22 to be exact which
includes vitamins a c d e k 1 k 2 biotin
calcium magnesium zinc iron a potential
downside of this supplement is that for
the full dose you are meant to consume
eight capsules per day which can be a
lot for some people but it is a very
high quality product and it is a really
solid ingredients list as the best
women's multivitamin with probiotics
these gummies are some of the best in
the category smartypants daily organic
gummies with probiotics they contain 10
milligrams of bacillus subtilis
probiotics that have a 99 survivability
rate that means that most of the
probiotics will reach your gut alive
without the need to refrigerate your
supplement it is worth knowing that
probiotics are the most effective when
you get some prebiotic fiber with them
but basically just keep your fruit and
vegetable intake high you should be
pretty good next up the best
multivitamin for women athletes active
women may need a different formula to
help with recovery and overall health
and this pick is a really solid option
for it legion's triumph women has 22 key
vitamins and minerals like b vitamins
that can help with energy production
amino acids that can help with tissue
repair and even grape seed extract which
might help with heart health so on top
of these ingredients you'll find an
array of multivitamin staples like
vitamins a c d e
biotin zinc calcium magnesium iron this
supplement is also third-party tested
and has no artificial dyes or anything
you have to take eight tablets a day
like four twice a day but if you're able
to handle that many pills this is a very
good if slightly expensive option with
really really solid research-backed
ingredients and again it's been
third-party tested to ensure purity and
accuracy of the label what about a
personalized multivitamin some companies
offer you the ability to make your own
formula for a multivitamin that's
totally customized to you and your needs
our favorite for this is care of you
take five minutes to fill up your online
quiz which asks you questions about your
goals lifestyle value nutrition and
curve will customize a pack of vitamins
minerals herbs and probiotics tailored
just to you the aim is to simplify the
process of meeting your daily
nutritional needs and to make it more
affordable than the kinds of multi
you'll get at a drugstore with a whole
bunch of extra ingredients that you
might not actually need to keep the cost
down we recommend staying away from the
specialty blends with herbs which add up
quickly if you do that this is a pretty
cost effective option that's also very
specifically tailored to you and there's
also like prenatal options as well for
certain times in your life so yeah very
very solid multivitamin pick that's
tailored just to you next up is the best
women's multivitamin with transparent
ingredients because it's one thing to
figure out which ingredients you need
but a lot of people also want to know
exactly where those ingredients come
from and how they produce because you
know after all they want to know what's
going into their body ritual essential
for women is a brand that we found to be
the most transparent about their
ingredients one of the key missions is
to provide the user with information
about where each of the ingredients is
sourced so on the website they provide a
map that shows you exactly which state
and specific country an ingredient comes
from while it's great they provide a
user with complete transparency about
where the nine ingredients here come
from that doesn't mean you only need
those vitamins and minerals though so
take a close look at the label and make
sure you're still meeting your nutrient
requirements after taking this and
following your regular diet lastly we've
got the best greens powder for vitamins
greens powders if you're not familiar
with them offer a plethora of vitamins
and minerals from whole foods sources as
well as extras like probiotics and
digestive enzymes and antioxidants
athletic greens is our favorite for this
this is a complete green powder with
like plenty of vitamins a c e b12 biotin
zinc selenium there's also a 75
ingredient superfood complex with ground
up fruits and vegetables it also has
enzymes and probiotics for gut health
and an antioxidant and herb blend while
many greens powders may taste like dirt
i've had a lot of them athletic greens
actually has a really nice sweet flavor
that i actually enjoy savoring which is
more than i can say for just like every
other greens pad on the market so it's
very nutrient dense and very tasty to
boot all right that about does it for
our list of the best women's
multivitamins and again if you want to
check out the full written version of
this video so you can go through all
this information at your own pace you
can just google it with bar bend plus
best women's multivitamins
[Music]
you